Why would the president
keep the leadership of the Secret
Service in place after his own personal
security was breached repeatedly?
>> What are historians going to say about
this 20, 30, 50 years from now? What are
PhD
>> They're going to say at very least
there's a mystery at the center of it.
>> He was not permitted to follow up on
these leads. Well, call me a conspiracy
theorist, but that that's the only place
I can go.
>> Tucker Carlson and CIA whistleblower
John Kiriakou recently got together to
discuss the dark link between the Trump
assassination attempt in Butler,
Pennsylvania and the Charlie Kirk
assassination. The first of which has
been memory-holed completely and we
still don't have answers about either of
these things. But what are the linkages?
What is at the center of this and what
does it have to do with Iran and the
current war for Israel? Tucker and John
both discuss this. Let's check this out,
see what they have to say about it.
Please like the video and subscribe to
the channel.
>> You know, almost seems like this is an
intentional effort to destroy the United
States by our own government.
Yes.
Um
Okay, so back I just want to ask one
last question about how we got here. So
two or three weeks after this war began,
the head of the National
Counterterrorism Center Joe Kent
resigned. In his resignation letter he
said, "I believe
He didn't say this in his letter, he
said it in an interview with me shortly
after the next day. He said, "I believe
the Butler assassination
attempt
the other assassination attempt in
Florida, a couple of breaches of Donald
Trump's personal security Secret Service
detail
um and Charlie Kirk's murder may all
have played a role
in convincing the president to go to war
with Iran.
What do you think that means?
>> I would not be at all surprised. You
know what? Let me Let me preface this by
saying I don't have any inside
information.
But I would not be surprised if
a person or multiple people got into the
president's ear
and said,
"This isn't a coincidence that there
were these three events.
There were these three events because
the Iranians are behind it. They've got
these cells. They're around the United
States. We can't identify them. We can't
catch them. But, they're gunning for
you." And Charlie Kirk was, you know,
a practice hit or Charlie Kirk was a
message or whatever.
And I wouldn't be surprised if the
president would believe something like
that. If If people he trusts
are telling him there's a problem, and
the problem originates in Iran, whether
it's true or not,
that he would respond to that.
>> Yeah, I think that's very conceivable,
and I think a lot of people
underestimate how potential, how easy it
really would be to curate kind of an
audience for the president that would
constrain him to particular choices and
particular directions, especially the
president who is, you know, has very
little free time at times. I mean, Trump
does golf and party, and let's not make
a mistake about that, but he's
constantly surrounded by pro-Israel
zealots. And when you surround someone
like that, you can shield them from what
the rest of us see, that actual dissent
see in the independent media. All we
know about Trump is his preference is to
watch Fox News, just like most boomer
cons and neo cons. That is what they do.
But, you can put people like John
Ratcliffe and Marco Rubio and Stephen
Miller around Trump, get him to see what
they want him to see, and this is very
conceivable. Now, we speak of this
Overton window, the idea of, you know,
kind of the acceptable range of
allowable opinions among Americans to
have, otherwise you're a pariah. But,
there's really an Overton window within
the presidency where these things can be
dictated by trying to persuade him of
all these false realities to lead him in
particular foreign policy directions.
And I think that's what happened here.
>> I A lot of people did tell him that.
That's a fact. I can confirm it. People
told him Iran is out to kill you. The
Butler assassination attempt the Iran
was behind it. People were saying that.
Fact.
>> Mhm.
>> But where that theory falls down is with
the Charlie Kirk assassination. So if
you were if you were trying to claim
that the Iranians were behind it and
there were leads from the National
Counterterrorism Center or the
ODNI
>> Mhm.
>> that suggested foreign involvement, who
knows if they go anywhere.
>> Mhm.
>> You would follow up on those leads.
>> have to follow up on those leads.
>> shut them down. And that's a fact.
And you know, it doesn't make you a
reckless conspiracy theorist
>> No.
>> or evil to ask what is that? Why
wouldn't you follow up on those
leads?
>> You know, I I'm one of these people that
believes that in almost all cases the
simplest explanation is probably the the
correct one. But
when word came out thanks to Joe Kent
and his brave
actions and revelations
that
he was not permitted to follow up on
these leads.
Well, call me a conspiracy theorist, but
that that's the only place I can go.
>> Well, what's the answer?
>> There had to be some sort of a
>> What's the other answer? I mean, I want
to find another answer. I don't want to
have any thoughts like this, Charlie. Of
course, he was a good friend of mine.
>> a good friend of yours.
>> But even if he wasn't, I would just I
live in this country. I don't But what
>> Yeah.
>> Are there any good answers to that
question?
>> No.
>> There don't seem to be any good answers
to that question whatsoever. And rather
than being allowed to investigate it,
what really happened and he's truthful,
he's right about this. Joe Kent as the
chief of counterterrorism division
within the DNA brought these different
angles of potential foreign involvement
to the FBI to Kash Patel's desk and he
Kash Patel put the kibosh on it said
that he wouldn't investigate it because
it would compromise his case. This is
actually raised and covered to a small
extent in mainstream media accounts. It
was completely memory hold right because
they were going with the lone gunman
narrative in Charlie Kirk and it was
Kash Patel and in fact the DOJ that put
an end to the possibility of
investigating foreign angles into the
Charlie Kirk assassination. That is
something that Joe Kent's talked about
on several shows including on Tucker
Carlson, but I agree if you really
wanted to boil in the idea that there'd
be propaganda for the war in Iran, you
would want to try to pin a foreign angle
of Iran in the Charlie Kirk
assassination. On that one, they haven't
done that and on the Butler
assassination
Kash Patel promised answers from the
start when he got into the
administration. We're going to give you
the answers. They never did. They never
revealed the social media presence this
guy did have which they said was
essentially a blank that he didn't have
a social media presence, but Tucker
Carlson did a 40-minute or so
investigative piece on Matthew Crooks
and the Butler assassination attempt and
this guy had a lot of footprint online.
Something that the FBI never showed
people. So what's the reason behind
that? We might never know, but in either
way, it does seem like deep state
operatives close to Trump had convinced
him to launch this war in in Iran at
least partially because of the idea that
they were trying to assassinate him.
Now let's take a moment to thank our
sponsor monetary metals.
Monetary-metals.com/vault because lovers
of liberty and sound money already know
why gold matters. It's preserved
purchasing power over thousands of years
while governments debase paper currency.
It's a hedge against inflation, but
despite this, most people think of gold
as something that just sits around and
you forget about. But, that just means
it does nothing for you. It doesn't earn
a yield. But, that's where Monetary
Metals steps in. They've created a
system where you can earn yield on your
gold paid in more gold and in fact,
depending on the opportunity, up to 4%.
So, Monetary Metals gives gold owners a
way to guard against inflation, earn a
return, and put their metal into
productive use instead of relying on the
fiat financial system, a corrupt one at
that. So, if you already own gold or are
thinking of owning some, this is well
worth looking into. Go to
monetary-metals.com/vault
to learn how you can start earning a
return on your gold. Monetary Metals has
my full enthusiastic endorsement because
it's the ultimate way to protect
yourself from the corrupt financial
system.
Now, let's get back into the
conversation.
>> There's literally no reason why you
wouldn't follow up on a lead.
>> Why would the president shut down the
investigation into Butler and to his own
attempted assassination?
>> I I I can't even fathom
a reason. Especially because this
president has taken such a strong stand
against the deep state. Right? If
they're
I mean, we all agreed that there's a
deep state. You don't have to call it
that. You can call it the federal
bureaucracy or whatever you want to call
it.
>> Permanent Washington.
>> who are going to be here when you leave.
>> Exactly right. So,
is somebody like the president who has
taken such a strong stance against that
deep state, you would think would be the
first person to want to run these
allegations to ground.
>> Of course. But, also just out of out of
self-preservation.
Um why would the president
keep the leadership of the Secret
Service in place after his own personal
security was breached repeatedly.
That's a That's a fact. These are not I
mean, I'm not None of this is
speculation. Like, that's all true. Why
What explains that?
>> I worked with the guy in Athens. He was
a contractor. He had been the He'd been
a long-time
um Secret Service agent and was the
creator, the founder of the Secret
Service's intelligence division. He was
He started under Eisenhower. He was in
Dallas with Kennedy.
And finally, he was successful in
in creating this intelligence division
to work with the CIA and the FBI to head
off threats to the president.
He starts getting these letters at the
White House from Sara Jane Moore of San
Francisco, California. And she's saying
things like, you know, "Ask not for whom
the bell tolls, it tolls for thee."
Well, he flies out to San Francisco and
he knocks on her apartment door.
And she answers. He's got his badge.
"I'm with the Secret Service." He said,
"Sara Jane,
you keep threatening the president in
these letters. What's going on with
this?"
And he told me she said, "Uh no, I
didn't mean it. My Social Security check
was late and I got mad and so I wrote to
the president and I threatened him, but
I didn't I didn't really mean to
threaten him." And he said, "You're not
going to try to kill the president, are
you?"
And she said, "No, I'm not going to kill
the president."
And 2 weeks later, the president goes to
San Francisco and she's there bang bang
bang bang bang trying to kill the
president.
Heads rolled, his being the first.
He was fired from the Secret Service and
then they cleaned out the entire
leadership of the Secret Service.
That's what normal people do.
>> Yeah, that's exactly right. This was in
1975. Sara Jane Moore tried to
assassinate Gerald Ford. There was
another woman that tried to assassinate
Ford within just weeks of that, but this
caused serious internal firings. Heads
actually rolled on this, but in the case
of Butler, Pennsylvania, no heads
rolled. It seems like they just made
excuses for the Secret Service, and
really nothing changed. Not only that,
that Trump doesn't even bring this up
anymore. You have to ask yourself why
that Trump, someone with that big of an
ego, didn't investigate this, but that
is what happened. Now, I'll take
exception to what John Kiriakou said
based upon that Trump was adversarial to
the deep state. I've just seen no
evidence of it. All of it has been
rhetorical, that he wanted to drain the
swamp, eliminate the permanent
bureaucracy, but he's really embraced
the swamp in so many major ways in terms
of launching the war in Iran, not
disposing of a single intelligence
agency, not cutting back drastically on
FBI or CIA or NSA staffing whatsoever,
covering up the Epstein files, a sex
trafficking ring that involves some of
the most prominent people not only in
the United States, but elites in other
countries as well, and really doing the
bidding of those that he supposedly, you
know, put an a stop to in his first
term, John Bolton and and Mike Pompeo.
Well, he's embraced the John Bolton and
Mike Pompeo, and for that matter, the
neocon foreign policy. So, he hasn't
really stuck it to the deep state. He
was never really known for that. Did the
deep state go after him in his first
term? Absolutely, that's what Russia
gate was, but he hasn't done anything to
undermine the deep state. Quite to the
contrary, he's aligned with it.
>> Yeah.
So, here we've got two legitimate
attempts to murder the president of the
United States or the president-elect or
the president, the former president,
whatever he happened to be when these
attacks took place.
And it's the same people.
The same people who let the bad guys
get close enough to him to take a shot
and hit him in the ear.
>> So, given that we both have conceded we
don't, you know, the answer to this
question.
>> Tell me as someone who spent a lot of
his life abroad working for the US
government as a CIA officer,
assessing the workings of other
governments
and drawing rational conclusions. So,
let's say
the facts as we just have agreed are
real, which they are, applied to, pick a
country.
>> Mhm.
>> Bahrain, where you lived for years.
>> What would you conclude?
The head of state of Bahrain
has had a couple documented
assassination attempts against him and
and possibly others that have never been
>> Mhm.
>> written about.
>> That's right.
>> And I think that is true.
>> Yes.
And doesn't investigate them.
>> No, they come down with an iron fist.
>> Oh, of course. They don't They don't
play in Bahrain or most other countries.
But if But if you found out that the
head of state, the emir of country X,
was not investigating an assassination
attempt against himself, what would you
conclude?
>> That he's weak.
That he's weak.
And either he's afraid of what he's
going to stir up
or he's just such a weak leader that it
hasn't occurred to him to follow through
on this.
>> Yeah, but it's an attempt on his life.
>> on his life.
>> Yeah.
>> shot in the ear.
>> Like I say, I don't think a single
American would have been surprised or
unsupportive if he had come down with an
iron fist. First of all, everybody in
Butler that day in the Secret Service
and everybody in the Secret Service
leadership should have had their badges
confiscated and walked to the door.
You're fired. And
>> Absolutely. That was the first step that
should have happened. And it's these
circumstances where there doesn't seem
to be a serious investigation that have
caused many more people than at the jump
to say, "Hey, this was an entire psyop.
This was actually not an assassination
attempt at all. That's the story they're
selling you." That's hard for me to
believe, especially given that he was
shot in the ear. There's documented
evidence of that. A man lost his life in
the crowd in Butler, as well.
But, at the same time, there wasn't an
investigation. So, what should I That
tell us? It's at least that the
aftermath of the assassination attempt
was a psychological operation to sweep
maybe parts of the truth under the rug,
and that's what I think we saw. I think
we're continuing to see that because,
again, it doesn't make sense for a guy
whose megalomania,
you know, can't go farther than Trump's
in some regards. He doesn't even care
about this. He doesn't talk about this.
Instead, he talks about being the
architect of Operation Warp Speed and
Epstein being a Democratic hoax and,
supposedly, the US
completely decimating Iran and having
achieved victory there. That's what the
president talks about, but nothing
regarding this assassination attempt. I
think we have to ask ourselves why.
>> You're not working in government again.
You allow an assassin, a child,
to get onto the roof of a building and
say, "Uh on my walkie-talkie, uh there's
a guy on the roof over there with a
high-powered rifle, and he's pointing it
at the president. Uh what should I do?
Do I have authorization to shoot?
What is that?
I I can't even imagine somebody behaving
in that way. Everybody should have lost
his or her job.
And instead, literally nobody lost their
job.
>> So,
that's so weird cuz normally there's
like a one-to-one between someone's
obvious interest in his actions. It's
like, that's a threat to me. I'm not
putting up with it.
But, here you have a case where it's a
clear threat to him, but he's
absolutely putting up with it.
You're ascribing that to weakness, like
he's just
weak. Just like he's got too much else
to deal with.
>> can't imagine and I don't think he's a
weak man. I think he's proven time and
time again that he's not.
>> like, what are we looking at?
>> something here. Yeah, there's something
deeper in the system that's not
permitting him to go forward or that's
not permitting the government, the rest
of the government to conduct an
appropriate investigation. What are
historians going to say about this 20,
30, 50 years from now? What are PhD
candidates
>> say at very least there's a mystery at
the center of it at the center of like
global events. And now that we've
embarked on this war against the council
of the entire US government, like
you just said there's no one in the US
government who was for this that we know
of anyway.
And he does it anyway in the wake of
those acts of violence.
Joe Kent says there's a connection.
>> Yeah, Joe Kent did think there was a
potential connection. He wasn't so sure,
but he brought those possibilities to
the FBI. And like Kiriakou said, there
is some missing piece here that the
public isn't privy to. That much is
obvious. And in so many ways what we're
witnessing to the Trump assassination
attempt, the Charlie Kirk assassination,
the lingering questions from those
things, and the Epstein scandal in a way
kind of is similar. It's like the '60s
are playing out again. There's so many
lingering questions still about the JFK
assassination, the MLK assassination,
even the Robert F. Kennedy assassination
with RFK Jr. thinking that Sirhan Sirhan
didn't actually pull the trigger. With
Martin Luther King, his own family
thinks that there's an FBI conspiracy to
kill King. And that was founded because
the FBI tried to persuade King to kill
himself. That much is documented with
Deputy
Sullivan writing him a famous letter.
It's only been publicized for the last,
I think, something like 15 years proving
that. And a Memphis jury deciding in
1999 that yeah, the FBI was involved in
a conspiracy to kill King. With the JFK
assassination, was the Israel lobby
involved? Was the CIA involved? Was
James Angleton, who was a double agent
of the United States and Israel
involved? Maybe yes, but in so many ways
we're seeing this with the Epstein
scandal, the Charlie Kirk assassination,
and the Butler PA assassination attempt.
And that's to say nothing about the Ryan
Ruth assassination attempt. That guy had
a self-published book
supposedly calling for recruitment to
the war in Ukraine against Russia. He
was a recruiter of sorts. We were told
that he had no money, yet he was
offering people money to fight and die
in the war against Russia. He also
praised the Syrian Liberation Army, the
CIA's chosen faction within Syria, in a
self-published book that you can still
get on Amazon today. Nothing to see
here, no questions. All these things get
memory holed. Trump never brings them
out, and you would think, if you were
someone again of the disposition of
Trump, not exactly a humble, subtle guy,
this would come up again. Instead, it's
Operation Warp Speed that comes up
instead. It's spend more. It's Thomas
Massie's bad. It's Israel good. It's,
you know, dispose of free speech rights.
It's extend FISA 702. That's what comes
up. And smearing his opponents, but not
the people that tried to kill him. We'll
try to smear Thomas Massie every chance
we get on Truth Social, but let's not
ever talk about the Butler or the
Mar-a-Lago assassination attempt. That's
what we're seeing here. So, like I said,
I think the '60s are playing out to some
extent. And this discussion's really
good. What's the answer? I don't know.
Hopefully we get more and more
information as time goes on, like we did
to some extent with the JFK
assassination. Still a lot of concealed
files. Kyriakou is told by his insider
sources that there's something like 10
to 15,000 more files on JFK that they
still haven't released. Who knows? We
still haven't seen 2 to 3 million
Epstein files. They've only released a
small portion of that to the public to
see.
And we're just supposed to have no
problems with this. No investigation
into foreign angles of the Kirk
assassination. No investigation proving
things that we later knew was true from
non-governmental entities like Tucker on
the Butler assassination. Where do we go
from here? I don't know. The public just
isn't informed because the government
closes its doors to the government. The
government is opposed to transparency
because transparency is the people to
know is for the people to know the inner
workings of their government. But the
governors do not want those inner
workings to be revealed. Some of them
ultimately trickle out. We know about
the evils of the CIA, the regime change
operations, all the foreign wars from
the jump start, the deep state
corruption, the ties to Epstein, ties to
Israel and Mossad. All these things are
just rancid. They stink to high heaven.
And on top of that, a Palantir-based
surveillance state that the CIA and NSA
are extending to make all of us tax
cattle that can be shut down in a moment
if we have a negative opinion. That's
what would happen if we have a CBDC and
an extended surveillance state, but that
might be in the future unless Americans
stand up now. All of it's kind of
intertwined into this deep state
corruption. Trump never went against the
deep state. The deep state did try to go
against Trump his first term. Certainly
did. Got him impeached at least one of
the the two times. He's going to
probably going to be impeached again
after the Democrats sweep Congress.
But he never really went against the
deep state. He did in fact embrace the
deep state. He does the deep state's
bidding. And I don't buy for a second
that no one in his inner circle wanted
to launch this war. I think they did.
That New York Times piece is interesting
and I have no doubt that there were some
naysaying voices that you shouldn't
launch this war, but it's going to be
impossible to convince me that Marco
Rubio, the lifelong neocon, anti-Cuba,
anti-Iran, and frankly anti-American
neocon didn't want this war. That's a
tough sell for me. But what do you guys
think? Do you think John Kiriakou and
Tucker Carlson are right about this?
What's the truth about Butler? What's
the truth about Charlie Kirk? Will the
public ever know it? And is there Is it
just a coincidence that Charlie Kirk was
spending his last months trying to
persuade Trump not to launch a war
against Iran that we eventually did get
a war in Iran. Let me know in the
comments down below. Like the video,
subscribe to the channel, subscribe to
Tucker. Great segment, really great
guest, of course. Love everything
Kiriakou has to say. listen to that man
for hours.
And if you like this video, please
consider joining as a YouTube member.
You can do that by clicking the join
button down below and doing that makes
you a member and thus immediately privy
to all of my videos before they go live
to the general public. You get access to
those before anyone else is a member and
I appreciate your support. And also, if
you want a free copy of my first book,
Compact of the Republic, go to the link
in the description. That will send you
to a website, just plug in your email
right there and I'll send it to you free
of charge. And I have no more things to
say than my demands and it's demands
against an Israel first corrupt deep
state embracing machine and I won't
apologize for them. No more war, no more
debt, no more inflation, and no more
empire.
Peace out, guys. Catch you in the next
one.